LUIS ROBERTSON

123 Your Street, Dallas, TX 12345 Lroberison@exartnple.coin (123) 456-7890

A Community Service Worker with six years of experience, specializing in delivering clinical services to elderly and disabled populations, A strong history of collaborating with registered nurses and medical teams to deliver medical treatment and social services, Adept at aiding vulnerable citizens in obtaining resources to improve quality of life.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN PUBLIC HEALTH

Dallas University, Dallas, IX, September 2010 - May 2014

KEY SKILLS

- · Clinical Services
- Social Services
- · Community Resources
- Program Development
- ◆ Case Management

CERTIFICATIONS

- Community Health Worker
 Certification (CHW), 2016
- Certified Community Service
 Worker (CCSW), 2015

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITY SERVICE WORKER
Fair Acres Medical Center, Dallas, TX
June 2017 — Present

- Provide support, community resources, and social services to elderly populations and adults with cognitive, physical, and mental disabilities
- Identify counseling services and caretaker services for clients based on physical limitations, medical conditions, and mental health needs
- Collaborate with clinical staff and the program director to develop activity programs for residents, including supervised trips from the facility, musical entertainment, and daily learning activities to improve cognitive skills

COMMUNITY SERVICE WORKER ESL Literacy Council, Chicago, IL May 2014 - June 2017

- Coordinated with registered nurses to provide treatment, administer medication, and patientcentered care to residents
- Conducted interviews with clients to evaluate living situations, ensure patient safety, and coordinate safe discharge into the care of families and guardians